Hello, my friends, and welcome to exercise number 75 in this exercise, we are asked to reverse this
attack using technology.
So we need to write a method that follows the recurring pattern and try to reverse the stack so.
This we have a stack, if it is like one, two, three and four, the four is a.
We need to print it again by four, three, two and one.
So for one, becomes at the top of the stack, OK?
This is how we reverse is.
That was the video.
And think about it how we could reverse it stack.
By the way, I have added that method called Peak.
I have missed it in the previous video and the implementation of the stack and returns that element
at the peak and at the above and there at the top of the stack.
So let's start making our stack reversing method.
This method stack reversed will depend on a math and new method that it is insert at, but let me create
the public.
Static void
insert at the bottom.
It took a perimeter into X, and this method will check if if this stack is empty, so I will create
here.
A stack I will cut their stack.
I will make it as static, so static.
Stack called Stack, OK, I will go here so I can now use Stack.
If it is empty, then we could use that Bush.
OK, it's very simple.
We are crushing tax if it is empty and we are inserting at the bottom, all else here else.
All items are held in function call stack on until we reach end of the stack.
When the stack becomes empty, then stack that size becomes zero.
Then the above if part is executed and that item is inserted at the bottom.
OK, you see the algorithm.
How the algorithms work.
Print X equal to stack dot peak.
OK, Stack Dot Bar.
And here.
I will put it why and insert at button this, I would call it again by using recursion insert at button
and I pass y or X again.
OK.
Otherwise, when we use recursion, we continue making this happens, this method will rebuild, it
will return it data whenever the last one, the last method that we used.
Returns a value.
So we we are going to make stack the bush.
And what I was talking about is this is the fact that Bush is not executed until insert at button will
be will be executed many times and the last thing the last execution will return a value.
Then when we have a returning value of this method, the tag that bush will be executed.
OK, this is how we make that recursion algorithm behind reversing and inserting and there, but at
the bottom.
So please go back to the recursion section if if you want to learn more about recursion, now we are
going to make a reverse function that reverses that given stack using the insert at button function.
So static void a reverse method and it will start checking if Stack is that size greater than the zero.
Then we are going to reverse it.
OK.
If it is equal to zero, then we are not going to reverse and think because there's zero.
OK, now the algorithm to reverse tells us to hold all items in function.
Call the stack until we reach end of the stack by making an index equal to the stack the peak.
We get the stack, the peak of the stack, the top level and we start by popping.
We pop the elements and we call reverse again.
So this is the recursion.
We have used recursion here and we have recursion here.
So this algorithm behind recursion will have two methods that works and depend on a recursion.
OK.
After that, here we are going to insert at bottom method and we are inserting Element X inside to insert
all the items held in the function called stack one by one, from the bottom to the top.
Every item is inserted at the bottom.
OK.
You see, guys, how this works, how the algorithm works behind the reversing.
We use the reverse function.
We have a recursion and we use an inverse insert at the bottom method that would use also recursion.
OK.
So how to test it?
Let me run before and show you our stack.
Let me print the stack here, going up in the stack and the print I need to put like spaces between
the method items.
OK, so we have here.
Often prevent system that our footprint line.
OK, let's run and see again.
OK, we have inserted these elements.
Our stack is one, two, three and four to the top level is for the stack.
After popping we we have popped the element four, so we have removed it from the above.
And now we have one two three one two three and we have three at the top.
Let's reverse this stack.
So.
System that the print here.
Reverse, reverse this back, so here.
Stack the reverse, or we can call reverse method directly because it is a static.
We can remove it.
And here we.
We need to OK, it's good so we can use tag dot certifiers.
Let's print again, the stacks of print, the stack again game, that's Iran, Nancy.
Reverse the stack, and here we go, we have reversed the Stack City two and one.
You see guys that we how we have used the algorithm behind recursion and we have.
Inverse, the stack one two, three two become three to one and become the element, and the top would
be one.
You see, this is very important and mainly ask that question in the universities and in the.